Mateo Campos

San Carlos, CA 94070 | matfc@live.com | (650) 339-4769 | LinkedIn | Portfolio

SUMMARY

2D Artist and animator with several years of experience using industry software. Looking to work on long-term projects, also dedicated to getting work done for the art/gaming industry. Able to communicate well with others and has a very friendly and positive attitude. Willing to experiment with and learn new software.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Services & Engagement, Target, San Mateo, CA | September 2024 – present

- Cooperates and communicates with a team to engage customers satisfying their needs.
- Delivers and engages with customers on their order pickups.
- Helps communicate with customers and reports to Team Leaders whenever issues arise, or deadlines need to be met.

Instructor, Bay Area Pathways Academy, San Mateo, CA | June 2023 – June 2024

• Taught classes about the introduction of coding, web management, Python, Roblox world creation, and creating music with online software.

Coding/Web Designer, Menlo Studio, Remote, CA | June 2022 – July 2024

- Collaborates with others on designing structure and content on Cañada College webpages.
- Uses HTML and CSS to tweak web pages to follow new designs.

Student Assistant, Cañada College, Redwood City, CA | November 2021 – May 2024

- Works with a group of professors to help assist them getting their Zoom conferences established with their students.
- Communicated with students on assistance on how to complete their assignments for their classes with software such as ToonBoom Harmony and Adobe.

EDUCATION

UX/UI Design Certificate

Google/Coursera, Online | November 2022 - December 2023

Completed training modules designed to prepare for entry-level employment. Training courses included: UX design process, building wireframes, low-fidelity, and high-fidelity prototypes, and creating mockups with programs such as Figma and Adobe XD. Created case studies, projects, and a portfolio to complete the certificate.

B.F.A, Digital Art & Media

San Jose State University, San Jose, CA, GPA: 3.41 | August 2017 – May 2020 Relevant Coursework: Advanced Digital Video, Digital Media Art, Intro Game Studies, Drawing, Color.

Associate Degree, Animation & Graphic Design, Certificate

Cañada College, Redwood City, CA, GPA: 3.47 | August 2021 – May 2024 Relevant Coursework: Digital Imaging, Advanced Digital Animation, Storyboard Development, Web Programming, Digital Page Layout, User Experience/Interface Design, Coding for Designers & Artists.

General Education

Cañada College, Redwood City, CA, GPA: 3.29 | August 2014 – May 2017 Relevant Coursework: Intro to Computer Graphics, 3D Character Animation, Drawing, Color, Web Design.

SKILLS

Computer: Adobe (Photoshop, Premiere Pro, XD), Figma, ToonBoom Harmony Advanced, Clip Studio Paint, GitHub, Sublime Text (HTML, CSS), Processing (Java), Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, Powerpoint), Google Apps (Sheets, Slides, Docs), Social Media (Twitter, Instagram, LinkedIn), Zoom, Slack, Canvas.

Languages: Fluent in English and Spanish.